# Kagiso Moepya

Cape Town, Western Cape, South Africa



kagisomoepya19@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/kagiso-moepya-87818015a

# Summary

I am a Software Development student at WeThinkCode\_.

I first studied at the University of the Western Cape where I became a graduate in the field of Commerce, majoring in Information Systems (IS).

Experiencing university was an experience and a half because that is where I got to develop my love for programming which led me to where I am today, being part of WeThinkCode .

In my journey, I have come to understand how my professions compliment each other and this is something which I would like to further explore on a larger scale.

# **Experience**

#### **Student Mentor**

WeThinkCode

May 2022 - May 2022 (1 month)

Assist bootcamp students solve coding related problems and make them understand the content better, furthermore what is expected of them within specific challenges.

# Information Systems 361 Tutor

University of the Western Cape

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021 (5 months)

# information systems 242/244 tutor

University of the Western Cape

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021 (1 year 1 month)

- -Assisted students with Javascript, MySql, Php, Html, Css.
- -Assisted them in assignment difficulties.
- -Marked scripts or projects completed by students

### Northink Examination Assistant

Northlink College

Dec 2019 - Dec 2019 (1 month)

-Quality Assurance and Quality Check of student scripts.

# **Quantitative Skills for Commerce 131/132 tutor**

University of the Western Cape

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 (1 year)

- -Assisting students with Commerce or Financial mathematics.
- -Marking Students Scripts.
- -Invigilating during tests.

# Examination Assistant

Ekurhuleni East College

Nov 2018 - Dec 2018 (2 months)

-Quality Assurance and Quality Check of student scripts.

#### **Education**

#### WeThinkCode

Higher National Diploma, Computer Software Engineering Sep 2021 - Jun 2023

#### University of the Western Cape

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Management Information Systems, General

2018 - 2020

Major : Information Systems Minor : Financial Accounting

#### **Skills**

SQL • Miro Collaboration Platform • Figma (Software) • GitHub • Gitlab • Financial Mathematics •

Java • Python (Programming Language) • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)